how you can get involved first go back
and watch the video series if you
haven't already like and subscribe to
this channel so as new content and new
questions are answered you will be able
to stay informed sign up for our email
list so that as there are tasks and
roles going forward and new projects or
new steps on our current projects you
will be able to know what is happening
as it happens attend our live board
meeting talking about transparency we
have our board meetings live every week
at 11 a.m. on this channel Pacific
Standard Time on Fridays Fridays Pacific
Standard Time 11 a.m.
come join ask questions ask questions in
the comments I will try to tackle any
question I have the ability to answer as
well as finding the solutions finding
the answers together that is the power
of this technology cooperative we are
going to do this together everybody is
invited to come create the tools and the
world that works for them thank you
please like and subscribe and give me a
right now take care